=The Origin of Eternity=
= أصل الخلود =
=Episode 5=
= الحلقة 5 =
Kiss me.
قبّلني.
It hurts.
هذا مؤلم.
(Something is strange about this room.)
(شيء غريب في هذه الغرفة).
(Is this where the Ghost Bridegroom lures the bride?)
(أهذا حيث العريس الشبح يغري العروس؟)
Qinghuan.
تشينغوان.
(This won't do.The smoke from the love potion is too dense.)
(لن ينفع هذا ، فدخان جرعة الحب كثيف جدًا).
(But Qinghuan has not recovered from her serious injury.)
(لكن تشينغهوان لم تتعافى من إصابتها الخطيرة).
(Her body won't be able to endure it.)
(لن يتمكن جسدها من تحمل ذلك).
Qinghuan.
تشينغوان.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
I don't feel too well.
لا أشعر أنني بحالة جيدة.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
لا تخافوا.  أنا هنا.
I'll be here and stay by your side.
سأكون هنا وسأبقى بجانبك.
I'll stay by your side.
سأبقى بجانبك.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
Qinghuan.
تشينغوان.
You're up. How are you feeling?
أنت جاهز.  كيف تشعر؟
Do you feel better now?
هل تشعر بتحسن الان؟
I could only do that
يمكنني فقط أن أفعل ذلك
to apply medicine on you.
لتطبيق الدواء عليك.
Forgive me for my abruptness.
سامحني على فجائي.
It's all right.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
I don't mind.
أنا لا أمانع.
You don't know any martial arts.
أنت لا تعرف أي فنون قتالية.
Why did you risk your life to rescue me?
لماذا خاطرت بحياتك لإنقاذي؟
Because I like you.
لان انا معجب بك.
Even if I die,
حتى لو مت ،
I'm willing to do it
أنا على استعداد للقيام بذلك
as long it's for you.
طالما أنها لك.
Don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why do you like me?
لماذا اعجبك؟
Because
لأن
you're the nicest to me in this world.
أنت ألطف بالنسبة لي في هذا العالم.
I don't know why
أنا لا أعرف لماذا
my heart
قلبي
beats very fast
يدق بسرعة كبيرة
whenever I see you.
كلما اراك.
I wanted to hide from you.
أردت أن أختبئ عنك.
But I couldn't help myself
لكنني لم أستطع مساعدة نفسي
to get closer to you.
لتقترب منك.
♪Migrating swan geese fly before my eager eyes♪
♪ إوز البجعة المهاجرة تطير أمام عيني المتلهفة ♪
I see.
أرى.
Bai Ze,
باي زي ،
it's the first time I see you smile.
إنها المرة الأولى التي أراك تبتسم فيها.
♪I have no one to drink with♪
♪ ليس لدي من أشرب معه ♪
♪My yearnings are scattered when the sun goes down♪
تشتت أشواقي عند غروب الشمس
♪Like snow flying all over the sky♪
♪ مثل الثلج المتطاير في جميع أنحاء السماء
Don't lie to me.
لا تكذب علي.
Why would I lie to you?
لماذا اكذب عليك؟
You're my favorite person in the world.
أنت الشخص المفضل لدي في العالم.
♪I fear the past perishes in a flash♪
♪ أخشى أن يموت الماضي في ومضة ♪
♪And more, I fear traveling the world alone♪
♪ وأكثر من ذلك ، أخشى السفر حول العالم وحدي
♪Reminiscing the memories amidst tipsiness♪
♪ استحضار الذكريات وسط النشوة ♪
♪Missing out on the loved one while growing old♪
♪ فقدان من تحب أثناء تقدمك في العمر ♪
♪I fear the past perishes in a flash♪
♪ أخشى أن يموت الماضي في ومضة ♪
♪I even fear thinking of the sky meeting the sea♪
♪ حتى أنني أخشى التفكير في لقاء السماء بالبحر
♪Every visit to the mortal realm, meeting you brings more suffering♪
♪ في كل زيارة إلى عالم البشر ، يجلب لك مقابلتك المزيد من المعاناة
♪There's no love in the world that brings no tears♪
♪ لا يوجد حب في العالم لا يبكي
Eldest Martial Brother has returned!
عاد الأخ الأكبر!
Eldest Martial Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Eldest Martial Brother, have you eliminated Ghost Bridegroom?
الأخ الأكبر ، هل قضيت على العريس الشبح؟
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Congratulations, Eldest Martial Brother.
مبروك يا أخي الأكبر.
I have to thank Qinghuan for her contribution
يجب أن أشكر Qinghuan على مساهمتها
to helping me complete this task.
لمساعدتي في إكمال هذه المهمة.
Bai Ze,
باي زي ،
my father obviously sent you to take on Ghost Bridegroom alone.
من الواضح أن والدي أرسلك لتتولى شبح العريس وحدك.
Why did she go with you?
لماذا ذهبت معك؟
I went down the mountain secretly.
نزلت الجبل سرا.
Bai Ze didn't know beforehand.
لم يعرف باي زي مسبقًا.
Shut up! It was your fault Bai Ze had to kill Ghost Bridegroom
اسكت!  لقد كان خطأك على باي زي أن يقتل شبح العريس
to atone for his misdeeds.
للتكفير عن ذنوبه.
Yet, you cause more trouble by going down the mountain.
ومع ذلك ، فإنك تسبب المزيد من المتاعب بالنزول على الجبل.
How can you be worthy of him?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون جديرا به؟
Martial Sister, why are you scolding Miss Qinghuan?
الأخت العرفية ، لماذا توبيخ الآنسة تشينغوان؟
It's not like you completed the tasks
ليس الأمر كما لو كنت قد أكملت المهام
Eldest Martial Brother had given you.
أعطاك الأخ الأكبر.
Eldest Martial Brother,
الأخ الأكبر
Martial Sister Linyue hasn't sent food to the dungeon for three days.
لم ترسل الأخت العرفية Linyue الطعام إلى الزنزانة لمدة ثلاثة أيام.
Can you discipline her?
هل يمكنك تأديبها؟
Linyue, I told you
لينيوي ، أخبرتك
to send him food and water before I left.
لأرسل له الطعام والماء قبل مغادرتي.
Why didn't you do it?
لماذا لم تفعلها؟
I want to starve him.
أريد تجويعه.
So that he knows
حتى يعرف
he's no longer the leader of the Demonic Sect.
لم يعد زعيم الطائفة الشيطانية.
If he doesn't hand over the Secret Arts of Youming...
إذا لم يسلم فنون Youming السرية ...
Linyue!
لينيو!
Do you still not know your mistake?
هل ما زلت لا تعرف خطأك؟
Bai Ze,
باي زي ،
don't be upset.
لا تنزعج.
This is between Bai Ze and me!
هذا بيني وباي زي!
I don't need an outsider like you to interfere!
لست بحاجة إلى تدخل غريب مثلك!
Qinghuan is not an outsider.
تشينغوان ليس دخيلا.
I've already proposed to her.
لقد اقترحت عليها بالفعل.
Soon, she'll be my wife.
قريباً ، ستكون زوجتي.
Really? Congratulations, Eldest Martial Brother.
حقًا؟  مبروك يا أخي الأكبر.
I forbid it!
أنا أحرمه!
You proposed to her without Father's permission
اقترحت عليها بدون إذن الأب
and violated the sect's rules
ومخالفة أحكام الطائفة
for planning your life privately.
للتخطيط لحياتك بشكل خاص.
I'll ask for Master's permission.
سأطلب إذن الماجستير.
What about me if you marry her?
ماذا عني إذا تزوجتها؟
Linyue, stop being ridiculous.
Linyue ، توقف عن كونك سخيفة.
Martial Sister Linyue!
الأخت العرفية لينيو!
Martial Sister! Martial Sister!
أخت عسكرية!  أخت عسكرية!
Martial Sister, are you all right?
الأخت العرفية ، هل أنت بخير؟
Wake up! Open your eyes, Martial Sister!
استيقظ!  افتح عينيك يا أخت الدفاع!
(Dehe Pavilion)
(جناح ديهي)
Master,
يتقن،
how's Linyue?
كيف حال لينيو؟
I've been teaching her the Qingyun Sect's mental cultivation.
لقد كنت أعلمها التربية العقلية لطائفة تشينغيون.
She was careless in her cultivation,
كانت مهملة في تربيتها ،
which imbalanced her life energy caused by energy disorders in her body.
مما أدى إلى خلل في طاقة حياتها الناتجة عن اضطرابات الطاقة في جسدها.
Imbalance of life energy?
خلل في طاقة الحياة؟
Is there a way to help her?
هل هناك طريقة لمساعدتها؟
She's safe for now.
إنها آمنة الآن.
But
لكن
I need someone to heal her vessels with internal power.
أحتاج إلى شخص ما ليشفى أوعيتها بقوة داخلية.
But I'm too busy with the countless matters of the sect.
لكنني مشغول جدًا بأمور الطائفة التي لا تعد ولا تحصى.
Bai Ze, can you take care of Linyue for me?
باي زي ، هل يمكنك الاعتناء بـ Linyue من أجلي؟
Master,
يتقن،
it's my duty as an elder brother.
إنه واجبي كأخ أكبر.
Good.
جيد.
Martial Sister, do you feel better now?
الأخت العرفية ، هل تشعرين بتحسن الآن؟
I still feel unwell, Bai Ze.
ما زلت أشعر بتوعك ، باي زي.
Bai Ze, you always heal me whenever I'm hurt.
باي زي ، أنت تعالجني دائمًا كلما تأذيت.
You're so kind to me.
أنت لطيف معي.
You're my Martial Sister.
أنت أختي العسكرية.
I ought to take care of you as your Martial Brother.
يجب أن أعتني بك بصفتي شقيقك العسكري.
But I don't want to be your Martial Sister.
لكني لا أريد أن أكون أختك العسكرية.
Martial Sister.
شقيقة عسكرية.
Miss Linyue.
ملكة جمال لينيو.
Qinghuan.
تشينغوان.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
Qinghuan!
تشينغوان!
Stop messing around and get some rest.
توقف عن العبث واحصل على قسط من الراحة.
I can't hear you! No, I can't!
لا أستطيع أن أسمعك!  لا ، لا أستطيع!
Go and make out with Miss Linyue!
اذهب وتعرّف مع الآنسة لينيو!
I wasn't making out with her.
لم أكن أخرج معها.
Why are you denying it when I saw it?
لماذا تنكره عندما رأيته؟
Are you jealous?
هل انت غيور؟
I'm not jealous.
أنا لست غيورًا.
You're jealous.
انت غيور.
I'm not.
أنالست.
I don't want to have a sty in my eye
لا أريد أن يكون لدي ودقة في عيني
after seeing something disgusting.
بعد رؤية شيء مقرف.
You got it wrong.
لقد فهمت خطأ.
You knew
علمت
Linyue is injured.
Linyue أصيب.
I was treating her injuries.
كنت أعالج إصاباتها.
You're lying.
انت تكذب.
Why do you have to hug her when treating her injuries?
لماذا عليك أن تعانقها عند معالجة إصاباتها؟
Qinghuan.
تشينغوان.
Qinghuan!
تشينغوان!
Let me explain.
دعني أشرح.
Get out of the way.
ابتعد عن الطريق.
Put me down!
انزلني!
I'll prove there's nothing between Linyue and me.
سأثبت أنه لا يوجد شيء بيني وبين Linyue.
You can just prove it. But where are you taking me?
يمكنك فقط إثبات ذلك.  لكن إلى أين تأخذني؟
♪I couldn't free myself from the entanglement of love♪
♪ لم أستطع تحرير نفسي من ورطة الحب ♪
So tell me.
إذن اخبرني.
How are you going to explain it?
كيف ستشرح ذلك؟
♪If only I could first see you in the next life♪
♪ لو كان بإمكاني رؤيتك أولاً في الحياة التالية ♪
♪I wish we could be together again♪
♪ أتمنى أن نكون معًا مرة أخرى ♪
♪For another thousand years♪
♪ لألف سنة أخرى ♪
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
تجول بعيدًا عن الحشد ♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪ كما تنتظر المزيد من الأشياء الرائعة
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
انعكاس غروب الشمس من الماضي
♪Thousands of sailboats drifted in the sea of clouds♪
جرفت آلاف المراكب الشراعية في بحر السحب
♪And docked at different piers♪
♪ ورست على أرصفة مختلفة ♪
♪Only the catkin willow and my graying hair remained♪
فقط صفصاف القطة وشعري الشيب بقي
♪Let's take on♪
♪ لنأخذ
♪Another year♪
♪ سنة أخرى ♪
♪I traveled alone toward daytime as I waved aside the night♪
سافرت لوحدي في النهار بينما كنت ألوح جانباً في الليل
♪The tapping rain♪
مطر التنصت ♪
♪Awakened the sorrow♪
أيقظ الحزن
♪I'm crying out in loneliness amid pandemonium♪
♪ أنا أبكي في عزلة وسط الهرج والمرج
♪I endured countless ordeals from worldly entanglement♪
لقد تحملت محن لا حصر لها من التشابك الدنيوي ♪
♪Knowing how difficult things are for the first time♪
معرفة مدى صعوبة الأمور لأول مرة ♪
♪After you overcome the vicissitudes of life♪
بعد أن تتغلب على تقلبات الحياة
♪Only then do you understand the fickleness of the world♪
"عندها فقط تفهم تقلب العالم"
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪